Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Dean Taggert Memorial, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Mar 21, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Visit to Insititute of Environmental Medicine, NYU, (Brief Remarks on Institute), Mar 23, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - J. Edward Farnum Public Lecture at the Woodrow Wilson School of Public & International Affairs of Princeton University, New Jersey, (Commission Findings, Graduate Education), Mar 26, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Working Lunch for Caroline & Joseph S. Gruss Visiting Professorship in Talmudic Law, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Mar 28, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Harold Weill Medal Presentation Dinner, NYU, (Greeting, General Intro), Mar 28, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Gallatin Division Great Artist Series- Interview with Zubin Mehta, NYU, (Message on Mehta), Apr 4, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dedication & PH Dinner for Ruth and George Farkas Auditorium of Alumni Hall, NYU, (Brief Remarks & Presentation of Award to Ruth Farkas), Apr 10, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Fran Todman Dinner, NYU, (Talking Points Honoring Frank Todman who gave $1 million to Tisch School of the Arts), Apr 11, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Brock Lunch, NYU, (Welcome Remarks for Warden of Nuffield College), Apr 12, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - National University Continuing Education Association Annual Conference, Georgia, (Continuing Education), Apr 17, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Presentation of "Award of Honor" Medals from Fine Arts Federation of NY to NYU, NYU, (JB Accepts Award for Support), Apr 18, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Nicholas Wahl PH Dinner, NYU, (Talking Points Honoring Director of the Institute of French Studies), Apr 18, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Heights Alumni Reception, NYU, (Talking Points), Apr 19, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Courant Institute "Executive Briefing" on Ada Computer Language & Compiler, NYU, (Brief Remarks on Ada), Apr 23, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Raymond Carr Dinner/News Briefing/Seminar, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Apr 23, 1984-Apr 25, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - NYS Regional Economists Society, New York, (State and Local Government Initiatives), Apr 24, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Founder's Day, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Apr 26, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Holocaust Remembrance Service, NYU, (Sermon on Holocaust), Apr 26, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Mayors Forum on Urban Policy, NYU, (Importance of Urban Research Center), Apr 27, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Induction Ceremony, Florida, (Importance of Education), Apr 27, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - University of West Florida Commencement, Florida, (Excellence of Education), Apr 28, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Westside Community Conference, New York, (State of NYC), Apr 29, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Medical Faculty Remarks, NYU, (State of University), Apr 30, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Grants Magazine Article, (Graduate Education), Apr 30, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - NYS Association for Supervision & Curriculum Development, New York, (Excellence in Education), May 6, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, NYU, (Overview, University Progress), May 7, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254642
  - Annual Alumni Dinner, NYU, (Overview, University Progress), May 15, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Israeli Poet Amichai Reception, NYU, (No Remarks(, May 16, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 25 Year Service Awards, NYU, (Award Presentation), May 16, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sidney Hook Lecture/Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks), May 17, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Global Crossroads Panel, Washington DC, (International Education, Graduate Education), May 18, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Drew University Commencement, New Jersey, (Schools, Colleges, & Academic Excellence), May 19, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cocktail Reception Honoring New Life Members of the Albert Gallatin Associates, NYU, (NYU Events), May 21, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Trustees Dinner, NYU, (Citations to Honorary Degree Recipients), May 23, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYU Commencement Exercises, NYU, (Education), May 24, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - GBA Partners Cocktail Reception in Honor of Dean William F. May, NYU, (Brief Remarks on Dean May's), Jun 7, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Albert Gallatin Fellows Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks, Award Citations), Jun 7, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Luncheon of the Propeller Club of the United States, Athens, (Greek-Americans), Jun 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Annual Alumni Day of Athens College, Athens, ("Current Trends in American Education: A Panoramic View"), Jun 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Community Schools of Athens Commencement, Athens, (Commencement Remarks-Education), Jun 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ecumencial Doxology Homily, New York, (Greek-Americans), Jul 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ecumenical Doxology Celebration of Independence Day, New York, (JB Homily), Jul 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Local 23-25, ILGWU Awards 1984 College Textbook Scholarship Awards Ceremony, New York, (Education), Aug 16, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - APSA Hubert H. Humphrey Award, Washington DC, (Brief Remarks Accepting Award), Aug 30, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "The Research University, Graduate Education and Public Policy", Indiana Univ., (Graduate Education), Sep 1, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - NYU/Scholastic Ins. Press Conference, Sep 10, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Brown Plus Thirty" Banquet, NYU, (Welcoming Remarks), Sep 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, (Orientation to New Students), Sep 13, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Planned Giving Seminar, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Sep 13, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Washington Square Park Crafts & Antiques Fair, New York, (Brief Remarks), Sep 22, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Urban Research Center Luncheon, NYU, (Host and MC Lunch), Sep 24, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Father Hehir Symposium, NYU, (Welcoming Remarks), Sep 24, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Sep 25, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Presentation of Garrigues (Grass Rain), NYU-Spain Inst. (Talking Points), Sep 25, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Holy Trinity Cathedral Lecture, New York, (Greek-Americans), Sep 26, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Visit of Central American Rectors, NYU, (Brief Welcoming Remarks), Sep 26, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Accent Magazine Article, (Importance of Education), Oct 1, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Deadalus Interview, (Federal Role in Education), Oct 1, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Dean West Reception at GBA, NYU, (Brief Talking Points), Oct 3, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - National Council for Children & Television Speech, New York, (Children and Television), Oct 5, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Spain Talking Points, Spain, (General-NYU Ties with Spain), Oct 6, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Italy Talking Points, Italy, (General-NYU Ties with Italy), Oct 6, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Sir Steven Runciman Dinner, NYU, (JB Talking Points), Oct 18, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Sir Steven Runciman Convocation, NYU, (JB Remarks & Citation), Oct 18, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Robert K. Massie Dinner, New York, (JB Talking Points), Oct 19, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Gallaudet College, Washington DC, (Inaguration of President Jerry Lee), Oct 19, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Bowsher Lecture, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks on GAO), Oct 22, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Presentation of Nation S. Kline Medal of Merit to Rosalynn Carter, NYU, (JB Presents Award), Oct 22, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - SCE Direct Marketing Press Conference, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Oct 23, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 26th Street Dorm Opening, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Oct 24, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 26th Street Dorm Opening, NYU, (Tisch Brief Remarks), Oct 24, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Wright State University, Ohio, ("Election '84: Implications for Education"), Oct 25, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Marie Schwartz Dinner, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Oct 29, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Gannon Seminar, New York, ("Resolved that Education is a Federal Concern: A Congressman's View, Oct 30, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Gannon Lecture, New York, ("Education on the National Agenda: Perspectives & Prospects"), Oct 31, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Japan Center Conference Lunch, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Nov 2, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Campaign Gala, NYU, ($100 Campaign), Nov 3, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Patents Day, NYU, (Freshmen's Parents Orientation), Nov 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - IFA Board Meeting, NYU, (NYU Events), Nov 7, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Fairfield University Convocation, Connecticut, ("Engaging a Whole World: The Humanities in the 1980s", Nov 8, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Rusk Institute Dedication, NYU, (Dr. Rush & The Institute), Nov 9, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Eppie Lederer PH Dinner, New York, (JB Talking Points), Nov 10, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - BPA Charles Haskins Dinner, NYU, (Dinner for Donors to BPA), Nov 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rubin Dining Hall Reception, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Nov 12, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Sir Ronald Syme Dinner, NYU, (JB Talking Points), Nov 14, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Convocation, NYU, (In Honor of NYU Faculty), Nov 14, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - American Council of Life Insurance, Boston, ('84 Elections & Education), Nov 14, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, ('84 Elections & Education), Nov 15, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture/Dinner, NYU, (Lecture by Henry Grunewald), Nov 15, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Law Alumni Day, NYU, ("The Elections are Over: What Next"), Nov 17, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Spanish Institute Cocktail Reception, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Nov 17, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - SCE 50th Birthday Party, NYU, (JB Presents Award to Koch), Nov 19, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Resources Network Lunch, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Nov 20, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Angelos Angelopoulos Lecture, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Nov 20, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Iakovos Convocation, NYU, (JB Presents Doctor of Humane Letters), Nov 25, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Atlantic Institute for Intn'l Affairs, Paris, ("The American Administration After the Elections"), Nov 29, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Banco de la Provincia de Buenos Aires Seminar, NYU, (JB Intro), Dec 3, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Dedication of Nichols Center, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Dec 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Second Bobst Awards Dinner, NYU, (Arts & Letters Award), Dec 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Long I Grotto Luncheon, New York, (JB Receives Award(, Dec 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Hellenic Medical Society of NY Dinner Dance, New York, (JB Receives Humanitarian Award), Dec 8, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Events), Dec 10, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Metro Center Benefit Lunch, NYU, (Metro Center), Dec 10, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Liss Lecture (Notre Dame), Indiana, ("The Place of Faith in Public Life: A Personal Perspective", Dec 11, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Harry/Lucy Moses Center Lunch, NYU, (Honoring Them for Their Gift for Disabled Students), Dec 13, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Brittany Hall Façade Project, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Dec 13, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Filomen Greenberg Reception & Dinner, NYU, (Thanks for the Law School Gift), Dec 17, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Business Int'l Chief Executive Officers Roundtable, Jamaica, (Economics), Jan 6, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Meeting of the NYU Medical Center Board, NYU, (JB Talking Points), Jan 8, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Norman Lear PH Dinner, New York, (JB Talking Points), Jan 8, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - National Retail Merchants Annual Convenction, New York, (Education & Business), Jan 14, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - CBS/NYU Seminar Manuscript Introduction, New York, (JB Intro), Jan 29, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Association of American Colleges, Washington DC, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Feb 10, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Barron's Editorial, New York, ("Teaching Experiences: Beware of Editors Bearing Myths), Feb 1, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Palm Beach Dinner, NYU, (Dinner Honoring Frank Spencer), Feb 12, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Alan Landsburg PH Dinner, NYU, (Thanking Him for Contributions to TSOA), Feb 19, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Brittany Residence Hall Open House, NYU, (Informal Student Gathering), Feb 21, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Testimony Before Committee on Education & Labor, Washington DC, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Feb 27, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Metropolitan Life Reception, New York, ($100 Million Campaign), Feb 25, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Annual Management Meeting of Cooper Industries, Houston, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Feb 28, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Winter Celebration, NYU, (Fundraising Dinner), Mar 2, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Law School UN Conference, NYU, (JB Participates in Program on UN), Mar 1, 1985-Mar 2, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Ephraim Urback PH Dinner,NYU, (JB Talking Points), Mar 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254659
  - David Kriser Dinner, NYU, (Reagan proposed budget cuts), Mar 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, (Orientation for Prospective Students), Mar 9, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of Christians & Jews, New York, (JB Receives Charles Evans Hughs Gold Medal), Mar 11, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Testimony before Budget Committee, Washington DC, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Mar 12, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NYU Day in Albany, NYU, (JB Presents Awards), Mar 13, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Education: The Quest for Quality (Oaklawn), Elkhart, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Mar 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Inst. Award Dinner, NYU, (JB Presents Award), Mar 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Raul Alfonsin Convocation, NYU, (His Leadership of Argentina), Mar 21, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - EACUBO Speech, New York, (Reagan Proposed Budget Cuts), Mar 22, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sir David Hunt Seminar, NYU, (JB Opening Remarks), Mar 25, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Edward Bernays Presidential Citation Ceremony, NYU, (JB Citation), Mar 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center Board meeting, NYU, (JB Talking Points), Apr 2, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dean Richard West PH Dinner, NYU, (JB Talking Points), Apr 4, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Mary Lasker Testimonial, New York, (Personal Recorded Message), Apr 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dinner for New Trustees, NYU, (Penthouse Dinner), Apr 9, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mayor Koch Introduction, NYU, (Intro of Mayor Koch at Trustees' Scholars Function), Apr 10, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Senate Remarks, NYU, (JB Remarks), Apr 11, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Intro of Jack Kemp at GBA Alumni Day, NYU, (Intro of Jack Kemp), Apr 13, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - NYT Editorial Lunch, New York, (Student Aid, Tax Issues, Financing Higher Education), Apr 15, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Adelphi University Convocation, Long Island, (Humanities), Apr 17, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Lord Quinton Dinner/Lecture, NYU, (Intro of Lord Quinton), Apr 17, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dinner for George McGovern, NYU, (Talking Points), Apr 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Dutch Treat Club Lunch, New York, ("The Importance of Education: A Personal Perspective"), Apr 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Founder's Day, NYU, (Brief Remarks, Intro of Abe Gitlow), Apr 25, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Northeast Conf. On the Teaching of Foreign Languages, NYU, (International Education, Foreign Languages & the National Agenda), Apr 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - GBA Conf. On Economics of Art, NYU, (Brief Greetings), Apr 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Briefing for NY Delegation, Washington DC, (Briefing to NY Members on Issues of Interest to NYU), Apr 30, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Bronfman Scholars Lunch, NYU, May 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Law Alumni Assoc. 97th Annual Dinner, NYU, (Greetings & Brief Remarks), May 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Commerce Alumni Dinner, NYU, (Intro of Abe Gitlow), May 8, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Miller Birthday Statement, Washington DC, Congratulatory Note to Con. George Miller), May 8, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Breakfast Symposium on Learning Disabilities, NYU, (Welcoming Remarks), May 8, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 20th Anniversary of the Older Americans Act, Washington DC, (Statement on JB Role in Evolution of Older Americans Act of 1965, May 8, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Clair Flom Penthouse Dinner, NYU, (NY Alliance for Public Schools), May 9, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - University Senate Remarks, NYU, (University Matters), Sep 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, New Jersey, (Relationship of Religious Faith to Political Order), May 10, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Rider College Education Day, New Jersey, (Education), May 10, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 1985 Medical Alumni Day, NYU, (Greetings, Acceptance of Honorary Membership in the Medical Assoc. Class of 1985, Intro of Thomas Murphy), May 11, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (University matters), May 13, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Older Americans Act Essay, Washington, DC, (JB Role in Evolution of Older Americans Act of 1965), May 16, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - President's Message, Students Guide to NYU, NYU, (Informal Message), May 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - CBS Grey Art Gallery Filming, NYU, (Brief Remarks on Role of Art Gallery in the Life of a University), May 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Industry Day at Courant, NYU, (Welcoming Remarks), May 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Press Lunch to Announce a Grant from Carnegie Corp. to Establish Center for Study of War, Peace & the News Media, NYU, (Importance of Center), May 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Grey Art Gallery Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks on Value of the Grey Art Gallery to NYC & of Tom Sokolowski to the Gallery), May 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Wagner College Commecement, Staten Island, (Federal Role in Education), May 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Medical Library Association Annual Meeting, NYU, (Medical Research), May 27, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Alumni Federation Dinner, NYU, (Greetings & Alumni Fed Controversy), May 29, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Micheal Schimmel High Tea, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Jun 3, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Trustees Dinner, NYU, (Intro of Honorary Degree Recipients), Jun 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - WSUC Baccalaureate Ceremony, NYU, (Brief Greetings), Jun 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Medical Commencement, NYU, (Greeting & Intro of Steven Muller), Jun 6, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - 153rd Commencement Exercise, NYU, (Remarks with Theme of History), Jun 6, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - College of Dentistry Graduation, NYU, (Dentistry), Jun 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Spanish Institute Seminar, NYU, (JB Moderates Two Seminars on Spain), Jun 14, 1985-Jun 15, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Reception & Buffet Dinner Honoring Edward E. Barr, NYU, (Brief Remarks Honoring School of Commerce Alumnus), Jun 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Notre Dame Essay on Education, Indiana, (Federal Role in Education), Jul 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - International Federation of Library Associations & Institutions- IFLA, Chicago, (Libraries), Aug 19, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Ladies Home Journal Interview, (Higher Education in the Year 2000), Aug 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - "Politics & Education Reform", (Article for National Forum), Aug 28, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Reception for Class Agents from the School of Law, NYU, (JB Brief Remarks), Sep 4, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Medical Center Executive Committee Meeting, NYU, (NYU Affairs, Tax Reform), Sep 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, (Welcome to New Undergraduates), Sep 12, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - American Council for the Arts National Conference, NYU, (Arts Funding), Sep 22, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Executive Meeting of the Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (NYU Plans for 1985-86), Sep 23, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center Conference, Washington, DC, ("Spain in the 1980s: The Domestic Transition & A Changing International Role"), Sep 25, 1985-Sep 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - SCE/Head Start 20th Anniversary, NYU, (JB Addresses Conference), Sep 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Stanley Fink Dinner, NYU, (Stanley Fink), Sep 26, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Kriser/Weiner Dinner, NYU, (Kriser Professorship), Oct 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, NYU, (Informal Welcoming Remarks), Oct 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Visit by Frank Hodsoll, NYU, Oct 1, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, (Oliva Reports on NYU State), Oct 10, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Mayor's Proclamation TSOA Day, NYU, (NYU Status), Oct 15, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (NYU Status), Oct 21, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Convocation for Prime Minister Peres of Israel, NYU, (Honorary Degree for Peres), Oct 21, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - 50th Anniversary of Courant, NYU, (Honorary Degree for Stoker, Courant's Early Leader), Oct 22, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Stephen & Beatrice Brademas Lecture, Oct 24, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Convocation for Alfred Gottschalk, NYU, (Honorary Degree for Gottschalk, President Hebrew Union College -Jewish Institute of Religion), Oct 28, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on the Handicapped of the Committee on Labor & Human Resources, Washington DC, (PL 94-142), Oct 29, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Higher Education Capital Finance Symposium Morgan Guaranty, New York, (Tax Reform & its Effect on Education), Oct 31, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Central Opera Service National Conference, New York, (Arts), undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - The Rita & Stanley H. Kaplan Center Dinner Dance, New York, (JB Greets Guests), Nov 6, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - The Ernest J. & Elena A. Bruno Memorial Lecture, New York, (Health Care), Nov 7, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254667
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, (NYU Status), Nov 7, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education and Labor, San Marcos, TX (20th Anniversary of the Higher Education Act:1965-1985), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - BPA Haskins Dinner, NYU, (Brief Remarks About BPA & Dean Dan Diamond), Nov 11, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dental Fall Alumni Day, NYU, (Brief Remarks at Convocation), Nov 15, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of the Dr. Louis Blatterfein Center for Preclinical Sciences at the NYU Dental Center, NYU, (Brief Remarks), Nov 18, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate Institute Breakfast, NYU, (Talking Points to Institute's Advisory Board), Nov 18, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Yale Club Speech, New York, (Higher Education- Problems & Prospects), Nov 19, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - JB Inducation into the Academy of Athens, Athens Greece (International Education at American Universities), Nov 26, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Don Forman Mini-Gym Dedication, NYU, (JB Short Dedication), Dec 3, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Education Issues in Higher Education Act Reauthorization-Title IX, NYU, (Memo on HEA), Dec 4, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mainstream/Church & Society International Recognition Banquet, New York City, (Handicapped Children), Dec 10, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - GBA Conference on Not-For-Profit Sector, NYU, (Not-For Profit Sector), Dec 11, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The University Senate Meeting, NYU, (NYU Status), Dec 12, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Campaign Lunch, NYU, (Fundraising Plans), Dec 17, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Briefing for Ted Fiske Interview, NYU, (NYU Achievements), Jan 6, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)